yourschoolmatch.com 2015-03-16

# YourSchoolMatch.com

## Privacy Policy

_Last updated May 5, 2013_

This YourSchoolMatch.com Privacy Policy (this “Privacy Policy”) governs your use of YourSchoolMatch.com (the “Site”) operated by Your School Match LLC (the “Company”, “we”, or “us”). The Site, and any related features, promotions or content provided by the Company or its affiliates shall be referred to collectively as the “Services”. This Privacy Policy is incorporated as part of the Company’s Terms of Service Agreement, currently available at http://www.YourSchoolMatch.com/terms. The Company and the Services are based in the United States.

This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Services and describes the Company’s collection and use of user information.

The Services are general audience, are not targeted to children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information from an individual under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from someone under age 13, please contact us at privacy@YourSchoolMatch.com.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

**Submitted Information.** We introduce individuals like you to service providers that can provide you choices regarding educational services and products. We collect information that you submit to us through the Site (“Submitted Information”), including personal information you may submit to us in connection with requesting information regarding educational products and services or contacting us directly by email. 

Your submission is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information to us. In addition, the Company may supplement Submitted Information with other information collected or obtained from third parties.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, Submitted Information, together with any other information we collect, including automatically-collected information as described below, shall be referred to as “Your Information.”

The Company also automatically collects and uses certain information during your use of the Services as described below. On its own, this information is not personally identifiable, but could be linked with personally identifiable information that may identify a particular individual; if such a link actually occurs, we will treat this information as personally identifiable information for the purposes of providing the Services to you. 

**Accessing and Using the Services.** When using the Services, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected, stored and used for business and marketing purposes, such as maintaining and improving the Services, conducting research, and displaying more relevant advertisements. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation: IP address, unique identifier number, operating system, browser information, URLs visited, pages viewed, search queries entered, and other Services and hardware information. If you access the Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other information for that device in order to serve content to it. 

**Tracking and Data Collection Technologies.** The Company may use browser cookies, web and DOM storage data, Adobe Flash cookies, pixels, beacons, and other tracking and data collection technologies, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. These technologies may be used to collect and store information about your use of the Services, including without limitation, web pages, features and content you have accessed, search queries you have run, referral URL information, links you have clicked on, and advertisements you have seen. This data is used for business purposes such as providing more relevant ads and content, and market research. The Company may also use these technologies and other similar tools to relate your use of the Services to personal information obtained from you or a third party. For example, cookie, click stream or other data about your activities using the Services may allow us to limit the offers and content provided to you through the Services to items we think you will find interesting and relevant to you, based on your prior online activities and preferences.

**Third Party Tracking and Data Collection.** Third parties that support the Services by serving advertisements or providing other services, such as tracking aggregate site usage or providing users with the ability to comment on or share content, may also use cookies, pixels and other tracking and data collection technologies described above to collect user information. The Company does not control these third parties and their use of these technologies is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies.

For more information about third party ad networks that use these technologies, see http://www.aboutads.info/. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies).

Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website at the following link - http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html.

Please note that blocking cookies or implementing other restrictions may interfere with the normal operation of the Services.

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

**Third Party Providers.** When you provide us with Submitted Information in connection with a request for information regarding educational products and services, we will forward your Submitted Information to a network of participating educational services and product providers, or their respective agents, brokers, affiliates, third party finder or marketing companies (“Third Party Providers”), who may then forward your Submitted Information on to educational services and product providers that may provide your requested information.

Please note that the use of your Submitted Information by Third Party Providers is not under our control and is subject to the privacy policies of those entities. 

**IF YOU SUBMIT A REQUEST FOR INFORMATION FROM THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS THROUGH THE SITE, THEY MAY CONTACT YOU DIRECTLY WITH INFORMATION VIA TELEPHONE AND EMAIL. YOU MAY RECEIVE TELEMARKETING CALLS AS A CONSEQUENCE OF SUBMITTING A REQUEST ON THIS SITE, EVEN IF YOU ARE ON THE NATIONAL DO NOT CALL REGISTRY OR ANY OTHER DO NOT CALL REGISTRY.**

**Company Use.** In addition to forwarding your Submitted Information to a Third Party Provider, we may share Your Information with our parent, subsidiary or affiliate companies without restriction. 

**Services Providers.** We may share Your Information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf including, advertising and marketing, developing or supporting products and features, processing payments, administering message boards, processing data or statistics, and supplementing or organizing information or data. These third parties may have access to Your Information as needed to perform their functions. 

**To contact you.** The Company may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the Services to any email address you may have provided to us or periodic alerts on your mobile device if requested by you. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each promotional email or other method of notification.

**To provide and manage the Services.** We use Your Information to provide the Services to you, to measure and improve the Services, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising, and marketing messages, and to provide you with customer support and respond to inquiries. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If the Company sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, the Company may transfer Your Information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**To protect the rights of the Company and our users.** There may be instances when the Company may disclose Your Information without providing notice or choice, including situations where the Company has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Company, our affiliated companies, or any of their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of individuals; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process.

**MODIFICATIONS**

The Company may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and each such modification will be effective upon notice to you (including posting on the Site). All material modifications will apply prospectively only. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly. You may also receive a copy of this Privacy Policy by emailing us at privacy@YourSchoolMatch.com. 

**THIRD PARTY POLICIES**

The Services include offers, links, and advertisements from third parties wishing to promote their products, services, or sites. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties. Once Your Information is forwarded to a Third Party Provider or other third party, or you click on an advertisement or link from a third party, Your Information is no longer under our control and you should review the applicable privacy policy of the third party service or site, which may differ from ours.

**SECURITY**

Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. The Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information transmitted to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem by emailing privacy@YourSchoolMatch.com and cease use of the Services immediately.

**LOCATION**

The Services are hosted in the United States and the Company is based in the United States. If you are a user located outside of the U.S., you understand and consent to having any personally identifiable information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the U.S. and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above.

**NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS - YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, if you are a resident of California and have submitted personally identifiable information through the Services, you are entitled to request information regarding the disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to privacy@YourSchoolMatch.com. The Company reserves the right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the email address specified in this paragraph. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@YourSchoolMatch.com or at the address listed above.
